Isn't this nice?
We haven't been on a trip
since we went camping.
Yes,
and it's our first time just
the two of us...
I didn't expect to stumble
into a hot springs town on our drive.
Yes, it was a good idea to stop by!
I don't do hot springs,
but the footbath is nice.
What?! You can't do hot springs either?
Well... I can do them...
And down I...
Hey!
At hot springs and public baths,
I'm at risk of being sat on.
It's not fun.
Ah, I see...
I can use them if I have help,
but I always hate to be a bother...
I end up thinking, "I can have
a hot bath at home."
I guess hot springs are
a bridge too far for both of us.
But this might also be my first time
feeling properly healed by a hot spring...
Yes, agreed.
Are you ready to head back?
I can't wait to eat these
hot spring eggs at home!
Sir, please, you can't—
I've had enough! I'm leaving!
P-Please, let's talk this out!
I knew it wasn't just my imagination!
I'm not staying in this haunted house!
It's not a haunted house!
What's that all about?
Please, come back!
It appears the local inn is haunted.
We've been called to investigate
hauntings from time to time...
Have they ever been real?
Paranormal activity tends to be
someone's fears getting out of control,
or the abilities
of previously undiscovered races.
You investigate hauntings?!
Do forgive the sudden request.
I am the proprietress of this inn,
and we've been plagued
by rumors of a haunting of late!
I'm afraid I'm here
in a personal capacity...
I'll put you up for free
while you investigate!
All-inclusive!
So please, stay and help me!
Th-This was supposed to be
a day trip, though...
You're free to visit my
agency at a later date.
But in the meantime, I'll keep
being swamped by awful reviews!
I can't afford to lose more customers!
But I'm serious—
I'll rent you my best room,
with an open-air bath!
It's built on
universal design principles,
so I guarantee a comfortable stay...
A private, open-air bath?
No one else around!
I'm afraid it's just not possible.
I have another job to do tomorrow...
I can go in by myself...
Um... I could rearrange our schedule.
I think it would be possible.
The attendant will show
you to your room!
Right this way!
The room's set up like this!
It does have nice scenery...
But the bath is visible
from inside the room...
How am I going to tell Shizuka-san?
If I just close the curtain
to block off the view,
I probably won't need to tell her.
Maybe this is what she meant
about me being too accommodating?
That should be everything.
Do enjoy your stay!
Akira-san, I want to
get right into the bath!
I'll speak to the proprietress
about the haunting.
Call me if you need any help.
Okay!
BATHS ARE ONLY AVAILABLE TO
OVERNIGHT CLIENTS AT THIS TIME
You really don't have
any customers, I see.
Yes, it's as bad as it looks.
We've had a string of cancellations...
THEY REALLY NEED TO FIX THAT.
IT WAS SCARY, CREEPY, AND I HATED IT!!!
I guess it is the reviews.
BLOOD COVERING THE FLOOR?!
TOO FREAKY FOR ME...
Blood covering the floor?
It's certainly an unsettling image...
It's impossible!
I'd certainly have noticed
blood on the floors!
Yes, and they say it
disappeared right after...
Had you heard about this before?
A customer once called the front desk
about it in the middle of the night.
We went to check later
and saw nothing of the sort!
SAW A PALE FIGURE AT NIGHT. TOO CREEPY.
LOVED THE FRESH FOOD, THOUGH.
What about the dragging sounds at night?
HEARD DRAGGING SOUNDS DURING THE NIGHT.
WAY TOO CREEPY!
You may hear customers' luggage
during the day, but never at night!
Dragging sounds... Is it related
to the bloodstained floors?
What about this "torso ghost"?
SAW A GHOSTLY TORSO FLOATING BY DURING
THE NIGHT. I THINK THE PLACE IS HAUNTED.
It seems to appear at night, too.
There's no ghost here!
I've worked at this inn for ages,
and never seen the likes of that!
Well, it's true that not a single
haunting I've investigated
had a real ghost behind it.
As you can see,
I'm completely at my wit's end!
We had no idea about
any of this until people
started complaining
and leaving those reviews!
Understood.
I'll continue my investigation, then.
No traces of blood
in the hallway that I can see.
Was it wiped up immediately after?
To hide the evidence?
The only witnesses are guests,
and it mostly happens late at night.
The reviews talk about impressions,
nothing particularly concrete.
Not nearly enough information
or evidence to go on.
I'd have preferred to approach this
with more time and equipment...
I can't believe I was bought off
with an open-air bath.
If I can't solve it today,
I'll have to come back another time.
I'm back.
Akira-san!
The attendant helped me into a yukata!
Drat. My gratitude is starting
to overtake my regrets!
You look beautiful.
Hooray!
The bath was just heavenly.
You should try it, too!
No, I should get back to work.
Yes, I suppose so.
I'm sorry for getting ahead of myself.
This time, you're not going to
let work take over your personal life.
Don't do it!
The reviews suggest the phenomena
happens mostly at night.
It should be fine to wait until then.
Isn't this a window?
Why did Akira-san close the curtains?
He's free to enjoy
the scenery if he wants...
Is he accommodating me again?
Darn it...
Shizuka-san. I'm sorry for the wait.
Akira-san, why did you
close the curtains?!
Ma'am.
Didn't the attendant say the view
from the room was incredible?!
Ma'am.
Stop worrying about me and just enjoy it!
You don't need to be
accommodating like that!
I've brought this on myself, really.
What?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I-It's fine, since I can't see...
Well, I also can't be seen...
B-But...
Even if you can't be seen,
you don't like having people look
into your clothing, right?
I was covered in lather, so that
does lead to some embarrassment...
I-I see.
Well, I'm invisible,
so it's not really
a rational embarrassment.
But now I'm catching your embarrassment!
I'm sorry.
Do not apologize!
L-Let's have a meal.
The hauntings don't start
until nightfall,
so let's take our time and enjoy!
O-Okay!
What was that just now?
Was that a paranormal phenomenon?!
It's surely too soon...
I'm checking it out!
Wait here, Shizuka-san!
W-Wait!
Don't leave me!
By myself, I'll be...
too scared... please...
All right.
I'll protect you, Shizuka-san.
I'm not scared as long as there's light.
I suppose that's not very reassuring.
That's not true at all!
If you don't mind...
Could I come with you
on your investigation?
Of course! I'd be happy to have you!
All right. Let's go.
Right!
Well, that was fast.
Fast?!
There's a mysterious fluid on the floor.
Is it blood?!
I'll walk us to where
I can see it clearly.
It's black.
Black blood?!
It's rather viscous.
Viscous blood?!
Wait, that smells like...
What is it?
I saw a person, cut in half,
floating along.
C-Cut in half?! Floating?!
Sorry, maybe that
was too frank a description.
No, don't apologize.
I'm not a child.
You don't need to mince words
when giving me information.
Shizuka-san...
The sound... It's coming closer!
I see. The mystery is solved.
You've really found the truth?!
Yes.
The ocean view from our room
is what made it all clear.
Ocean?
I'll get right to the point.
The truth behind the paranormal
phenomena and the haunting...
It's...
These people!
My employees?!
A-Are you playing a prank on me?
C-Certainly not!
No, they're just going
about their jobs normally.
But it's so normal to you all,
you don't perceive it as paranormal.
"Normal"?
Ma'am, you mentioned the attendant
was leaving early today.
Y-Yes, that's true.
She's had to pull so many
late nights recently...
You were on your way
home earlier, weren't you?
Y-Yes...
But I left something behind,
so I came back to get it...
I'll get home early today!
Huh?
I forgot my kimono cord!
So much for getting home early!
Achoo!
Thank goodness I found it.
It was the sound of your
employee moving around.
Impossible! All this fuss
over a few ordinary noises?!
The incidents happened mostly at night.
And you mentioned she'd
been pulling late nights...
Yes, when it's late, I'm often in a hurry
to get the last of my work done...
As for the "bloody" floors,
when I talked to the
attendant in the hallway...
The reviews have been
complaining about this.
I'm not sure...
What's this all about?
Well...
Oh, there I go again!
I'm sorry. I've had a bit of a cold...
It's his ink.
I'd thought it smelled familiar!
Don't you have a handkerchief?!
Of course I do!
But sometimes I don't get to it in time,
or the ones I have get
all soaked through...
And the thing they have in common
is what helped me crack the case.
The torso was a rather pallid color.
Well, it could be...
You know.
Hello!
I see.
Hello.
This merfolk with a black tail.
S-Something so simple
caused all this fuss?
What they have in common
is being on the night shift.
When customers run into them at night
when there's no one around,
they likely get scared
and lock themselves in their rooms.
By the time they come out,
the ink has already been cleaned up,
and there's no one to be seen or heard.
S-So we were scaring the customers
just by going about our business?
Your inn is by the sea,
so a lot of aquatic races work here.
These things are normal for all of you,
but tourists haven't seen
anything like it before.
So they assumed it was paranormal.
And that explains why we didn't notice!
I never thought that
the sounds that were normal
to us would seem eerie to other races...
I've slipped on the squid ink
before myself...
But I always wipe it up right away!
Achoo!
I'm soaked.
Well, now that we know the cause,
we can discuss tomorrow how to deal
with it all, including reviews.
Of course! Thank you so much!
It feels great to solve the mystery!
I'm sorry we had to put off our meal.
But the food here is so delicious!
Yes.
The baths here are amazing, too!
I hope things turn around for them!
Indeed.
And now that the case is behind us,
we can have a good night's sleep.
You're going right to sleep?
You were incredible today, Akira-san.
I want you to kiss me.
We have an early day tomorrow.
Let's get to bed.
Right.
Good night.
Good night...
Akira-san...
It's possible this is
just my imagination, but...
Sometimes, it feels like
something's holding you back.
W-Well, but it has been a long day.
I know you're tired. Sorry.
Maybe Akira-san's just not
big on physical affection.
There are people like that.
Wait, maybe I'm just
not visually attractive?
I don't know what that's like
for people who can see,
but I've heard that it's a factor...
I get it. I'm ugly!
I've never really thought
about my face before...
What a shocking truth
to have to face now...
I'm sorry I'm ugly.
Where did that come from?!
You won't canoodle with me!
Seriously, where
are you getting this from?!
I get it. It's hard to admit to.
All right. Let's talk this out.
It's just...
I'll have to talk
about my last girlfriend,
so it might make you uncomfortable.
Do you still want to do it?
Yes.
At my last job... when I was
working at a big detective agency,
I was in an interspecies romance.
She tried hard to understand me
as an invisible person,
and I tried hard to understand her, too.
I felt like there was a time when we
both really trusted each other, too.
But, one night, it was like
she couldn't bear it anymore...
Or rather, I suppose it took
a lot of courage to say...
that I frightened her.
She couldn't help but feel afraid of
being touched by someone she couldn't see.
Just being who I am triggered
an instinctive fear in my partner.
She always looked so happy...
But I think she was just
trying not to hurt me.
I felt like I'd done
something awful to her.
Er... What was that?
Where's that mouth of yours now?
Shizuka-san?
Is this it?
That's my right cheek.
Got it.
That's my nose.
Then...
My upper lip.
Is that full credit? Half credit?
Let's say full credit.
My eyelid.
It was a little wet.
How insensitive.
Would you like to spend
the night like this?
Y-Yes!
If you'll get off me for a minute,
I'll pull the cover over us.
Aw, I thought we could
stay like this awhile!
You'll catch a cold.
Get your yukata back on straight, too.
I don't know how to fix it.
You'll have to do it!
Of course.
You're enjoying yourself.
I can smell you.
I love this smell!
You know, you've never
actually told me you love me.
I haven't?!
I love you! I love you so much!
You don't have to get
so panicked about it.
I love you!
You gotta believe me!
And I'm dearly in love with you.
EPISODE 9: "BEING WHO I AM"
TO BE CONTINUED